kaki narase sonzai wo
rock away your existence
koko ni iru to
shouting that you are here
arata na tabi ga ima hajimaru
a new journey begins now
kawari yuku kisetsu no naka wo ikinuku tabi ni bokura
as we survived through the changing seasons
chie to tsuyosa wo te ni ireta kedo JUST LOOKS LIKE SURVIVAL GAME
we gained knowledge and strength (just looks like a survival game)
nagareteku jikan no naka ni
but the forgotten memories
okizari ni shita omoi wo
of the feelings abandoned within the flows of time
wasureta koto sura wasurete ita
have also been lost
kuzure kaketa toki kodoku wo shitte
when sinking down we learned loneliness
deaeta bokura hitori ja nai
but now we've met each other we are no longer alone
sarake dase kanjou wo banjou no omoi wo
unveil your feelings those high emotions
namidame ga unmei wo kaete yuku
those tears will change your fate
yami ni uchi narase kodou wo
pound your heartbeat against the darkness
kitto aeru yo onaji itami no hata no moto de
we're sure to meet under the same flag of pain
Naruto!
There was an emergency transmission
from the training room!
What in the world happened?!
Actually, the star was stolen.
The enemy is a ninja
who flies using chakra!
No way...!
I've never heard of
a flying Shinobi.
Byakugan!
I lost him...
But what Naruto said is true.
To think he can fly
using chakra...
That's an incredible Shinobi.
So it was true.
What?! You didn't believe
what I said?!
You could say that.
What's up with that?
Do I have that little credibility?!
{Natsuhiboshi
The Memento Lullaby
So the star of
the Village Hidden in Stars
is a meteorite, huh?
Yes...
The First Hoshikage...
That's what they call
the village leader.
He discovered that if
you train by the "star..."
Chakra is strengthened.
Ever since then...
the Hidden Star has been
in a unique position
even among the ninja hidden villages.
But it says in these documents
that the training hasn't been conducted
these past ten years...
The leader who called himself
the Third Hoshikage
prohibited the training...
But about a year ago...
It seems they started again
after that Hoshikage died...
But why? Why do something
like prohibit training?
Who knows?
It's a classified matter of
the Village Hidden in the Stars, so...
But there were various rumors
circulating around about it...
Rumors?
Yeah... Rumors about most
of the Ninja who trained dying...
Chakra is forcibly strengthened
by the power of the unknown star.
There may have been
adverse effects on the body.
"STARS"
What...?
The star was stolen?!
Yes! The people who were
training were at the scene,
but they were all knocked out
by an enemy jutsu...
Pathetic!
You say that,
but that ninja had incredible chakra!
Naruto, is it that incredible?
Yeah! Turning chakra
into monsters or wings.
It's the first time I ever saw that!
Is that true, Sumaru?
Yes!
It's the Ninja Art: Kujaku,
no mistake!
That's the jutsu passed on
in the Village Hidden in the Stars, huh?
Yeah... As for that Jutsu, only those
who have mastered the star training can...
Sumaru!
Tenten...
The secrets of a jutsu are not to
be spoken of or asked about lightly.
Especially with a jutsu that can only
be passed on to those of that village...
I'm sorry...
Lord Akahoshi,
please give me an order!
The star being stolen
is my responsibility.
No...
The star was stolen
even though we were commissioned
a mission to protect it.
It's also our responsibility.
We will get the star back by
our own hands, no matter what!
Yes... I will leave the search for
the star to the Leaf Shinobi...
Sumaru, you keep an eye
on your injured comrades.
But only those in the village
know village matters...!
It's an order!
Hey! Are your friends who got beaten up
by the enemy ninja okay?
That's none of your business!
What...?!
At the end of the day, you're still
ninja from some other village!
You're not my friends or anything!
What's with him?!
Neji, you're talking about
taking responsibility,
but we haven't even seen
the scene of the theft.
That's right...
And we don't have any leads.
No, we do.
You didn't pick up on it?
Akahoshi the village leader
knows something!
What do you mean by
knowing something?
Come to think of it,
when Sumaru was talking about
the Kujaku something or other,
his expression changed.
Then that means the culprit is
someone associated with this village?
So, like I said, what does this mean?!
I'll make a go around the village
and look for something that
could make for a lead.
Lee and Tenten, you keep watch over
that village leader called Akahoshi.
I understand!
Leave it to us!
I don't get it!
What the heck should I do?!
Let me see...
You investigate from Sumaru's angle.
All right! Leave Sumaru to me.
Then, I'm off for a run!
Same as always...
Naruto sure is
an impetuous person, isn't he?
Natsuhiboshi, why are you so red?
Because I had a sad dream last night
My eyes are red
From the tears I shed
Swollen as I cried
Natsuhiboshi, why've you lost your way?
I'm searching for a child
Who has gone afar
My sad dreams come once more
Hey Sumaru!
What are you doing?!
Nothing! I was just looking
at the stars!
Stars?
Come to think of it, you can see
the stars well in this village.
That red star's sure pretty...
Natsuhiboshi...
It watches over me all the time...
Hey... Hold it. I want to go
visit your friends.
Look, here...
I've brought the Hidden Leaf specialty
Roasted Chestnut Bean Jelly!
Go if you like!
It's right near the training room!
A cold-hearted guy as usual...
What? Is nobody here?
Sorry to bother you.
Where is everyone?
Oh, is somebody sleeping?
"AMAGURIAMA CHESTNUT BEAN JELLY"
Stop it... Hokuto.
I can tell... He's not an enemy.
Mizura...!
You little!
A girl...?
Who are you?
I'm a ninja from the Village Hidden
in the Leaves, Uzumaki Naruto!
I came to this village
to protect the star!
You are...?
I'm sorry for my rough behavior!
It's cool. I just came to visit...
Where's the Roasted
Chestnut Bean Jelly?
Oh! That's it!
Oh, no!
There's no mistake...
Then it was that person who
made off with the star, after all...
So you're saying
that one's still alive...?
Then this will be difficult.
That one being the final ninja
completely trained
in the power of the star means...
Not an opponent we can handle
with the likes of our Jutsu!
Don't get flustered...
If the culprit is who we think it is,
we already hold that one's weakness
in our hands.
I get it...
Then let's grab that person up.
Wait...
First we must avert the eyes
of the annoying flies!
I'm sorry...
My name is Hokuto...
I felt chakra from someone not
of this village...
I carelessly...
Well, the flavor won't change, so eat up.
Okay...
Oh my... It really is good!
Right? Right?
Say... What happened to the others?
The thief just put us to sleep...
There wasn't such a great deal
of damage.
I see.
You okay?
Thanks for saving my butt back there!
Is there something wrong with you?
No... nothing at all...
After Mizura began the star training,
he started to feel poorly...
Hokuto! Don't be talking about the star
to someone from another village!
Are you okay, Mizura...?!
I'm sorry. I got carried away...
Other village...
You guys are kind of cold-hearted.
Especially that Sumaru guy...
I'm sorry...
But there's a reason
why Sumaru became like that.
What?
It happened ten years ago...
Sumaru's parents, who
were protecting the star,
were killed by ninja from
some other village...
who came to steal the star.
So probably, he's...
So that's what it was about...
That's why he got like that.
So where is Sumaru...?
And where are the other guys?
It seems everyone went
to take back the star.
Naruto?
They've come out.
Right...
We should take them on
fair and square here...
Idiot! There would be
no point to surveillance!
I'm not much one for
sniffing around secretly.
Be quiet. They'll notice us!
Leave the trailing ninjutsu to me...
Follow me quietly!
But...
It's a mission!
I understand...
Let's go...!
Secretly, secretly...
It's okay... They haven't noticed.
But I get the feeling this kind of thing
goes against my Way of Ninja...
Don't complain!
Secretly, secretly...
You don't need to say secretly, secretly!
But is this really a trailing ninjutsu?
Have we been noticed?
Wait...
It appears we weren't noticed...
Let's continue trailing them!
Right! They turned right!
Roger!
They vanished...
Did they give us the slip?
Could it be, they noticed us?
Wait! We're not enemies!
That's right!
We came here on a mission from
the Village Hidden in the Leaves!
Oh, Leaf Shinobi, you say?
Then aren't you guys trailing
the wrong people?
That might be so.
But there's the possibility that
you guys have transformed
into people from this village, so...
Brave words.
I apologize for the rudeness...
But now the star has been stolen.
And we don't have any leads...
So that's why
you were investigating us, huh?
That was unnecessary...
Oh, well... We will take back
the star with our own hands.
You guys just make sure
you don't get in our way!
They kind of tick me off...
But it's as Neji said...
It seems there's some kind
of secret in this village, eh?
Seems so...
Everyone... join hands!
Listen up! Pick up the same
star chakra as us!
There he is!
You can't cut a rope
woven with chakra!
Give back the star!
That's our life!
Neji, have you seen Sumaru
and the others?
You weren't keeping watch of him?
Actually, it seems most of the guys
went out to look for the star.
I see...
Hey... is it okay to be all relaxed?
Hey, is something wrong?
There's massive chakra
at the Valley of Death.
Did he appear again?!
— Let's go!
— All right!
Give back our... star...
Give it back...
Hold it!
Eat this!
Ninja Art: Kujaku!
I won't let you get away!
Hold it!
Farewell!
What?!
Damn you!
Wait!
Let me go! Let me go, I say!
Calm down!
Up ahead is the valley filled
with poison gas...
Okay...
You would've been dead meat
in a few seconds without that mask on...
Damn it. We almost had him.
So that was the Shinobi
who stole the star?
Yeah! Absolutely no doubt about it!
Why? Why is it necessary
to go out of his way
to take Sumaru away although
he carried out his goal already?
Does that have something to do
with the star being targeted
ten years ago?
At that time, it seems Sumaru's parents
got killed protecting the star.
What?!
kinou wa Call Sign zenbu keitai de
yesterday's call sign was broadcast all from my phone
norenai Fuzz Guitar henna kouen de
in a strange park I play the fuzz guitar without enthusiasm
Yellow Moon
yellow moon
ima mo mittsu kazoete me wo akete
even now, counting to three I open my eyes
Shadow Moon mada yume wo miteru
shadow moon, I am still dreaming
me wo mite me wo mite se wo mukeai nagara
look at my eyes, look at my eyes, as we face one another's back
me wo mite itsu aeru
look at my eyes, when can we meet?
Every Day Every Night omoi tsuku kotoba de
every day, every night, with every word I can think of
chirakatta mama no kimochi wo ima sugu
right away, my messy feelings as is
mahou no Chord Change nemurenai machi
a magical chord change in a restless city
higawari na Jazz Guitar sotto mainaa de
a daily jazz guitar played in a soft minor key
We need to re-investigate
the village leader and his relations.
Please leave it to me!
I've got an ace strategy.
A strategy?
I can't count on Tenten's
trailing Ninjutsu, can I?
What did you say?!
Do whatever you want.
Just follow through with it.
All right! Here I go!
We'll see how good you are.
Then, me, too...
Hold it, Naruto.
Next:
"The Price for the Secret Technique, Kujaku Myouhou."